原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     白夜君  草草  苏葵  小酸奶
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     spohy  大葱  啾啾啾
后期     吉吉
总监     小酸奶
深入黑暗  第一季 第七集
编译缺陷3489
辛迪·休斯
要嫁给完美男人  身边都是棒棒的人  好幸福
#辛迪和马克的婚礼
丹尼尔·斯坦纳
等不及明天了  肯定特开心#辛迪和马克的婚礼
编译缺陷3489
头条:@辛迪休斯001 愿给每一个男人吹箫  祝你开心  马克
回复
编译缺陷3489
头条:@辛迪休斯001 愿给每一个男人吹箫  祝你开心  马克
#辛迪和马克的婚礼#戴绿帽
逗你玩
逗你玩呢
I'm just fucking with you.
找个牙医吧
简直是狗精液
根本没人在乎
小屌综合征
谁去宰了这金发婊子
#没啥亮点的婊子
警报  没屌蠢蛋们
没屌
编译缺陷
辛迪·休斯的照片
辛迪·休斯冲向屌群
这里有疱疹
小心荡妇
荡妇
村公交
后庭被人戳了吗
砍掉她的脑袋
干死那婊
拉瑞  你来不来啊
Larry, you coming or what?
我已经订好位子了
I already made the reservation.
瑞秋·亚当姆斯
那我有权叫你取消掉
Well, I reserve the right to tell you to cancel it.
少来了
Stop.
妈妈爸爸来酒店了
Mom and Dad are here at the hotel.
大家都知道这让你多难受
Everyone knows how hard this is for you,
但我们只是想见你
but we just want to see you.
你是我唯一想见的人
Look, you're the only one that I want to see.
我去啊
Holy fucking shit.
快看辛迪的推特
Get on Cindy's Twitter feed now.
天呐
Oh my God.
丹尼尔·斯坦纳
回复@编译缺陷
你是谁啊
詹妮弗·埃里克森
回复@编译缺陷
别丢人了
有个天才骂得她好惨
Some genius just totally flamed her.
编译缺陷3489
回复@辛迪休斯001
头条@辛迪休斯001 愿给每一个男人吹箫  祝你开心  马克
#辛迪和马克的婚礼#戴绿帽
这个编译缺陷是谁啊
Who the hell is ProgrammingFlaw, anyway?
-什么  -该有人给他发个奖章
- What?  -Someone needs to give that guy a medal.
你要来的吧
Okay, so, you're coming, right?
我...我不想去嘛
I just-- I just don't want to.
那我去找你好了
Well, then I'll come to you then.
我猜猜  你待在一个
Let me guess: You're staying in some
很低俗妖艳的地方吧
flamboyantly vile place, right?
快说嘛
Tell me. Come on, tell me.
好吧
Ugh, fine.
我住在
I'm staying at the...
粉红汽车旅馆酒廊
Pink Motel and Lounge.
听上去真有趣
Ooh, sounds so very.
我稍后就到
I'll leave here in a minute.
粉红汽车旅馆酒廊
回见  拉拉宝贝
Ciao, Lar-Bear.
办公室
有人吗
Hello?
哥们  我骗到你了吧
Oh, man, I had you going there.
是啊
Yeah, man.
你骗到我了  真厉害
You got me good, that was good.
你有什么问题吗
You got a problem?
什么  没有
What? No.
你有的
Yeah, you do.
XYZ
X-Y-Z.
-你真是难以置信  -我逗你玩的
- I can't believe you. - I'm just fucking with you!
愚人节啊
April Fools, big boy!
真好玩
That was a good one.
我们再来一次吧
Let's try that again.
有什么事吗
How can I help you?
我想入住
I'm just looking to check in.
-你是店主吗  -不是
- Are you the owner? - Nope.
我是切斯特
I'm Chester.
拉瑞
Uh, Larry.
我是杰拉德
Oh, hey, I'm Gerald.
喊我杰拉就行  拉瑞  认识你很高兴
You can call me Gerry, Larry, pleasure's all mine.
嗯
Yeah, um...
我可以找你登记入住吗
So can I just check in with you, or?
嗯  我今晚要身兼两职
Yeah, I'm pulling double duty tonight.
现在是淡季
It's off-season,
店主要削减开支
so the owners are cutting costs.
没法生他们的气
Can't stay mad at them.
他们是对很可爱的老夫妇
They're real sweet old-timers.
说得是啊
Huh, I hear you.
我开车开了好久
Well, I've had kind of a long drive, so
真的很想睡会儿了
just love to get to bed.
嗯  当然
Oh yeah, of course.
房间75美元
Room's 75 bucks.
如果你有现金就不用交税
No tax if you've got it in cash.
太好了
Great, great, yeah.
不喝别人给你的饮料是种侮辱
It's an insult to leave a beverage a man's given you.
-杰拉德  抱歉  -给你
- Gerald... sorry. - Here you go.
这是基本礼貌啊
It's common courtesies.
我可以...当然
I mean, I can have... uh, sure.
真乖
Attaboy, attaboy.
谢谢
Thanks.
好吧  我们为什么而喝
Okay, what are we drinking to?
敬美妙的笑声
To the beautiful sound of laughter.
-好  -阿门  敬那
- Okay. - Amen, to the beautiful
美妙的笑声  上帝保佑你
sound of laughter, God bless you!
好了
Now.
切斯特  认识你真高兴
Chester, it has been great getting to know you.
拉瑞  真不错
Larry, nice.
我知道
I know.
我来擦擦
I'll wipe that up.
人真棒啊
Huh. Nice guy, huh?
他可温和了
Aw, he's a teddy bear.
很有幽默感
Great sense of humor.
是吗
Oh, really?
你来做什么的
So what are you in for?
就是家族婚礼
Oh, just this family wedding thing, it's...
那个最讨厌了
Oh. Those are the worst.
或许你能走桃花运
Maybe you'll get your bone buried.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
你是怎么了
What's going on with you, man?
坐下吧
Sit down, come on.
跟切斯特说说  坐下
Vent to Chester, sit down.
没事  就是...
Uh, um...no, it's, it's...
不好说  应该没事的
I don't know, it should be fine, actually.
答错了
Wah, wah! Wrong answer.
就是
No, I mean, it's just...
有好多我好久没见过的人
there's a lot of people I haven't seen in a while,
那是...
so that's...
不止如此
There's more to it than that.
好吧
Okay, okay, um...
我不知道  我讨厌跳舞
I don't know, I hate dancing,
这是首先
first of all.
食物从来都不怎么样
The food's always a letdown.
食物  不是吧  说吧
The food, really? Come on.
好吧  我不得不出了75块
All right. I had to shell out 75 bucks
买烤板  因为那是礼物登记单上
for cookie sheets because they were
最后一样东西
the last thing on the registry.
烤板
Aw, cookie sheets!
难道猪小姐还会自己烤饼干吗
Like Miss Piggy's ever gonna bake her own cookies, right?
是啊...但我告诉你
That's, I mean... I'll tell you what, though.
我希望她喜欢那些烤板
I hope that she likes those cookie sheets,
因为说真的  它们可比
because, honestly, they're gonna last
她的婚姻能持久得多
a lot longer than her marriage.
那听上去是个你不会娶的姑娘
That sounds like a girl that you wouldn't marry.
不  婚姻不适合我
Nah, marriage is just not my thing.
敬永远的孤狼
To lone wolves forever.
嗯
Yeah!
Yeah.
我真的想睡了
So I really am just really tuckered out,
-能把钥匙给我吗  -当然
- so could I get the key? - No sweat.
我只需要你的信用卡
All I need is your credit card
我就能给你登记
and we'll sign you right in.
我已经给了你75美元的房间钱了
I already gave you the 75 bucks for the room.
我知道了
Oh, I get it.
以牙还牙是吧
Tit-for-tat, right?
不  我真需要你的信用卡
No, I'm just gonna need that credit card.
你说真的吗
Are you serious?
当然了  伙计  这里又不是小客栈
Afraid so, man, I mean, I ain't operating a halfway house here.
不  我不是那意思
No, I'm not saying that,
但我刚进来时
it's just that when I first came in,
你记得吗  就刚刚
you remember, like, a minute ago,
你还说  如果我给现金
you said if I give you cash,
你就不收税了
then you wouldn't charge tax?
然后  我拿了现金
And then, I took out the cash
把钱递给了你
and I handed you the cash.
那个机车党
I mean, that guy, that biker guy, he--
首先  他叫杰拉德
First of all, his name is Gerald,
其次  正是因此  我从不
and second, I never check in anyone
不办妥手续就让人入住
without proper paperwork for this reason.
我明白  但这太疯狂了
I understand that, but this is crazy.
你打的什么主意啊
I mean, what are you trying to pull here?
听着
Look, man.
你走了进来  我们喝了点酒
You came in here, we had some drinks,
我们笑了笑
we had some laughs,
如果你要房间  可以
and if you want a room, that's great.
但我需要带照片的身份证和信用卡
I'll just need a photo ID and a credit card.
好吧  那倒空你的口袋
All right, well, empty your pockets, then.
什么
Excuse me?
你倒空你的口袋
You empty your pockets
你会看到里面有我的钱
and you'll see my money in there.
你把我的钱...这太荒唐了
You put the money-- this is ridiculous.
你要我报警吗
I mean, do I have to call the cops?
随你  报警吧
Go ahead, call the cops.
顺便  我还有个点子
And while you're at it, I got another idea.
把你的手伸出来
Put out your goddamned hand,
因为你的房间钥匙在这里
because I got your room key right here.
伙计  你真该看看你的样子
Oh, man, you should have seen yourself.
我在逗你玩呢
I'm just fucking with you, man.
-好吧  -你真该
- Oh, okay. - You should have
看到自己  "这太荒唐了  我要报警吗"
seen yourself, "This is ridiculous! Do I have to call the cops?"
-不是的  -抱歉了
- No, you know... - Sorry, man.
要我叫更夫吗
You want me to call the bellman?
不用
No.
很好  因为我们没有
Good, because we don't have one.
好吧
Okay.
请整理我的房间
粉红汽车旅馆酒廊
写评价
编译缺陷3489
全世界最热情好客的地方  愚人节
这地方烂透了  满是虱子的破地方
发布评论
编译缺陷3489
已成功发布评论
辛迪·休斯
辛迪·休斯跟马克·亚当姆斯在一起
幸福  还有17个小时  #辛迪和马克的婚礼
还有17个小时  #辛迪和马克的婚礼
恭喜这对幸福情侣
恭喜
上我吧  大小伙子
Take me, big boy.
下面是我们本周的观众视频
Here's our viewer video of the week,
来自马歇尔
straight from Marshall.
切斯特·康科林向你发起了好友请求
切斯特·康科林
向你发起了好友请求
没错  查克  南柑橘这里
That's right, Chuck, it is still chaos out here
仍因多车连撞
on South Citrus at that multi-car pileup
而双向拥堵
that has caused gridlock in both directions.
详情还在不断传来
Details are still trickling in,
但距目击者称  一辆皮卡车
but witnesses report seeing the pickup truck
在路上蛇形驾驶  然后转向
swerving erratically before veering into
撞上了迎头而来的车  导致了连锁反应
oncoming traffic, causing this chain reaction
造成了一名年轻女子死亡
which left one young woman dead
数人情况危急
and several people in critical condition,
包括一名婴儿
including an infant.
据目击者称  司机
The driver, who witnesses say
明显喝醉了
was visibly intoxicated,
随后逃离了现场
then fled the scene.
治安官找到了嫌疑人的车辆
Sheriffs found the suspect's vehicle,
一款新皮卡车
a late-model white pickup,
被弃在距车祸现场几街区的地方
a few blocks away from the scene of the accident,
嫌疑人似乎...
where it appears as if the sus--
接听啊
Oh, come on, come on, come on.
这里是瑞秋
Hi, you've reached Rachel.
我现在不能接听
I'm away from the phone right now,
但我会给你回电  请留言
but I'll call you back if you leave a message.
你去哪了
Where the fuck are you?
你好  粉红汽车旅馆酒廊
Hello, Pink Motel and Lounge.
切斯特吗
Hi, uh, Chester?
举世无双
The one and only.
我是6号房的拉瑞
Oh, um, hey, this is Larry in Room 6.
嗯  拉瑞  我知道你是谁
Yeah, Larry, I know who you are.
我想问问我到之后  是否有人
Yeah, I was just wondering if anyone checked in
来过
since I got here.
我妹妹本该来见我的
My sister is supposed to come meet me,
我不知道  她迟到了好久
and, I don't know, she's pretty late.
我不知道她有没有来过
I don't know if she came in
或打过电话什么的
or called, or anything.
好吧
Oh, well, uh...
没人来过  但我查查留言
no one's come in but let me check the messages.
-或许我漏接了电话  -好啊  谢谢
- Maybe I missed a call. - Great, thanks.
拉瑞  我有坏消息
Hey, Larry, I got some bad news.
怎么
Yeah?
是你妹妹的事
It's about your sister.
是有通留言
There was a message.
我真不想告诉你这种事
I hate to be the one to tell you this, man.
她不来了  拉瑞
She's not coming, Larry.
她找到了根大屌吹
She found a big cock to suck on,
然后她死了  上了天堂
then she died and went to heaven.
搞什么啊
What the fuck?
拜托  这根本没道理
Come on, man, it doesn't even make sense
如果她出事了
that someone would call me
怎么会有人打给我
if something happened to her.
天呐  切斯特
Jesus, Chester.
如果你需要什么给我打电话
Just call if you need anything.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
冷饮
让老杰拉帮你吧  伙计
Let old Gerry help you out, buddy.
谢谢
Thank you.
你碰我了吗  小子
Did you just touch me, peckerwood?
我  我没有
No, no, I didn't, sir.
你碰了  是吧
Yeah, you did, didn't you,
小子
little man?
知道这写的是什么吗
You know what this says?
不知道
No, sir.
孤狼
Lone wolf!
知道它代表了什么吗
Do you know what it represents?
-不知道  -代表了我的盔甲
- No. - It represents my armor.
你不能碰公路战士的盔甲
And you don't touch a road warrior's armor
除非你准备好了要战斗
unless you're ready to fight
或大干一场
or fuck.
你准备战斗了吗
You ready to fight?
没有
Uh, no.
不要
Oh, no.
那好吧
Oh. Well, cool.
你刚勉强躲过了被爆菊
You just narrowly avoided an ass pounding, dude.
7号房  如果你想走运的话
Room 7 if you feel lucky.
你能至少接我电话吗  我好担心
你在哪
提醒
约翰·P回复了你的评论
是啊  那地方就是疾病和犯罪的温床  关门吧
提醒
约翰·P回复了你的评论
是啊  那地方就是疾病和犯罪的温床  关门吧
我真需要你的信用卡
I'm just gonna need that credit card.
犯罪
"我要报警吗"
"Do I have to call the cops?"
大屌吹
Big cock to suck on.
疾病
孤狼
Lone wolf!
关门吧
说真的  你在哪  给我发短信  我没法再一个人待在这里了
6号房  拉瑞
爱你的  妹妹
真好笑  切斯特
Very funny, Chester.
辛迪·休斯
要嫁给完美男人  身边都是棒棒的人  好幸福
#辛迪和马克的婚礼
艾米·汉森
回复@辛迪休斯001
7小时倒计  肯定很棒的#辛迪和马克的婚礼
编译缺陷3489
你以为@辛迪休斯001 最差劲的是出轨吗  不  7小时后还会刷新下限
发送
编译缺陷3489
你以为@辛迪休斯001 最差劲的是出轨吗
不  7小时后还会刷新下限
准备迎接大结局吧
#辛迪和马克的婚礼
瑞秋
Rachel...
嗯  我就过去
Hey, yeah, I'll be right there.
谁啊
Hello?
不  我没事  请稍后再来吧
No, I'm okay, just come back later, please.
不  我在洗澡  你可以待会儿再来吗
No, I'm in the shower, can you come back?
拉瑞  你没事吧
Larry, you okay in there?
切斯特
Chester?
当然是我
Yeah, man, of course it's me.
不是所有清洁工都说西语的
Not all cleaning people speak Spanish.
那是很种族歧视的假定
That's kind of a racist assumption.
听着  我是想在你
Listen, man, I was hoping to get to you
用厕所前找到你
before you used the bathroom.
门有点问题  有些客人
It's got a tricky door that's been giving guests
遇到过麻烦  我之前想说来着
some problems, I meant to tell you this before
但我们之前聊得太开心了
but we were having such a good time.
别逗我了
Just stop joking around, man.
什么  不  我是喜欢开玩笑
What? No, come on, man, I like to joke around
但我不会这样搞你的
but I wouldn't mess with you like this.
随你说我妹妹
Just say that my sister is, like,
在给大屌吹箫什么的  但放我出去
sucking a big dick or whatever and just let me out, man.
拉瑞  我发誓  我会因为
Larry, I swear I could lose my job
这种事丢了工作的
over something like this, man.
雪莉和约翰尼说得很清楚
Sherrie and Johnny made it very clear
我得告诉住在六房的客人这扇门坏了
that I had to tell guests in Room 6 about this door.
你得帮帮我  兄弟
You got to help me out, man.
让我出去  我什么也不会说  好吗
Just let me out and then I won't say anything, okay?
行  老天  你真是个好人
All right. Geez, you're a good man.
我觉得我需要你
Okay, I think‐‐ I'm gonna need you
用力推这扇门
to put a lot of pressure on the door.
什么
What?
这是最老套的耍人技巧了  哥们
That is the oldest trick in the book, man,
我不会上当
I'm not gonna fall‐‐
我明白你为什么会这么想
Okay, I understand why you think that,
但我没有逗你  拉瑞
but I'm not fucking with you, Larry.
你在推吗
Are you putting pressure?
嗯  我在推
Yes, I'm doing it.
好的  现在你需要使劲  好吗
Okay, good, now you're gonna need a lot of leverage, okay, man?
你必须得用力
You've got to really do it,
用身体全部重量压上去
put all your weight against it.
-我在推了  -好  跟我一起用力
‐ I'm doing it! - All right, just do it at the same time,
准备好了吗  数到三  一
you ready, on three. One‐‐
哥们  我们做到了
Oh, man, we did it, buddy.
你他妈有什么毛病啊
What the hell is wrong with you?
好吧  你没有笑
Okay, okay, I see you're not laughing.
但从我的角度看这件事
But look at it from my perspective.
没错  我是把门给堵上了
I mean, yes, I was holding the door shut.
怪我
Bad on me.
但说实话  我没想到你真会上当
But honestly, I never thought you'd fall for it.
既然我们都已经说到一半了
And once we were in the middle of it,
我怎么能中途停止呢
how could I stop?
拜托  只是个玩笑
Come on, man, it was just a joke.
是我  切斯特啊
It's me, Chester.
你真可悲
You are pathetic.
你知道吗
Do you know that?
没人喜欢你这种人  你就是
Nobody likes people like you, you just‐‐
你就是没有眼力见
you never get the hint.
你只是不停地得寸进尺
You just push and you push
蹬鼻子上脸
and you push and you push.
我告诉你吧
Well, let me tell you something.
没人觉得你搞笑
Nobody thinks that you're funny!
就...
Just...
你觉得我不搞笑  是吗
You don't think I'm funny, huh?
那你觉得什么搞笑
Well, what do you think is funny, then?
来啊  给我讲个笑话
Come on, tell me a joke.
切斯特  我们都累了
Chester, we're both tired,
今天发生了很多事  所以能不能
it's been a long day, so can‐‐
给我讲个笑话
Tell me a joke.
来啊
Come on.
你管没有身体和鼻子的人叫什么
What do you call a man with no body and no nose?
什么
What?
没人知道[音同]
Nobody knows.
真不错  拉瑞
That's a great one, Larry.
我就知道你会讲笑话  拉瑞
I knew you had it in you, Larry.
太好笑了  哥们
That was great, man.
-好吧  -行
‐ Okay. ‐ All right.
祝你晚安  哥们
Have a good night, man.
喂  瑞秋
Hey, Rachel, uh,
我不知道你在哪
I don't know where you are,
但我得离开这旅馆了
but I've got to leave this motel,
这里太奇怪了
it's just weird here,
而且我也不知道你为什么没收到我的信息
and I don't know why you're not getting my messages,
但如果你能给我回电
but if you just want to call me back,
也许我就把车停在路口
maybe I'll just wait in my car
在车里等你  看你会不会经过或者...
down the road and see if you come by or...
简直太蠢了
It's just so stupid.
拜托了  我希望你能收到这些信息
Just please, please, I hope you get these messages, and...
我有点担心你出车祸了
I'm kind of concerned you were in a car crash.
我希望没有
I hope not.
该死
Aww, shit.
之前我让事态发展得有些难堪
I really let things get out of control earlier.
我不知道自己怎么了
I don't know what came over me.
你也许是个好家伙  但你知道
You're probably a good sport, but you know,
如果你给了老鼠一块饼干它还会开口要牛奶
you give a moose a cookie and he asks for milk.
我得寸进尺了
I was asking for milk.
对不起
I'm sorry.
嗯
Yeah.
我无法阻止你离开  但是
Well, I can't stop you from leaving, but
如果你非走不可
if you have to,
请接受我的道歉  作为朋友分别
please accept my apology and part as my friend.
行吧
Okay, then.
如果瑞秋来了
If Rachel shows up,
我会告诉她你不得不离开
I'll tell her you had to leave.
好好享受婚礼
Enjoy the wedding.
拜托给我回电  这不是闹着玩的
瑞秋
我一个人在这待不下去了
他怎么知道她的名字
How did he know her name?
911  请问有什么紧急事件
911, what's your emergency?
你好
Hi.
我在粉红汽车旅馆酒廊
I'm at the Pink Motel and Lounge,
这里的店主
and there's the owner
空调  冰箱  彩电
或员工  他在照看...
or a guy who's‐‐ who's looking after‐‐
粉红汽车旅馆
你们得派人过来
I need you to send someone out...
*小蜜蜂*
*honey bee*
*我猜没有其他可以说的*
*Guess there's nothing else to know*
*除了我爱你*
*Except I love you so*
办公室
所以我在我的车里
You know, so I'm in my car.
我必须得退房  因为他整晚都在耍我
I had to check out because, I mean, he's been messing with me all night.
但他说了"瑞秋"  就是我妹妹的名字
But he had said "Rachel," which is my sister,
可他不可能知道她的...
and there's no way that he knows what‐‐
就是他
that's him.
就是  就是他
That's‐‐ that's him.
先生  我能和你谈谈吗
Sir, can I talk to you for a minute?
找到我的儿童毛片了吗  治安官
Found out about my kiddie porn, huh, sheriff?
我开个玩笑
Aw, just kidding.
都还算是合法的吧
They're all legal, barely.
别跟我开这种玩笑  先生
Don't even joke about that, sir.
你怎么知道她的名字的  切斯特
How'd you know her name, Chester?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
瑞秋
Rachel.
我从没告诉过你她的名字
I never told you her name,
如果她没来过  你怎么知道她的名字
so if she hasn't been here, then how do you know it?
因为你告诉我了  你个傻帽
Because you told me her name, you dope.
你真的就因为你忘记告诉过我
I mean, did you seriously call the cops because
你妹妹的名字就把警察叫来了
you forgot you told me your sister's name?
我...
I...
行了  交给我吧  先生
All right. I'll handle this, sir.
约翰尼和雪莉在哪
Where's Johnny and Sherrie?
我替他们看店呢
I'm just covering for them.
来我办公室谈吧
Step into my office.
好了
All right.
我们先冷静一下
Let's just calm down here.
你站在那
I want you over there.
你  去另一个房间
You, other room.
我们要谈谈  先生
You and me gonna talk, sir.
我能帮什么忙
So what can I do?
我只是帮着看店
I mean, I'm just keeping the place open,
这些破事不能让我负责啊
I can't be in charge of the crazies.
听着  今晚是满月
Right, well, listen, it's a full moon out here
你不是今晚唯一一个要面对疯子的人
so you're not the only one with crazy people tonight.
粉红汽车旅馆酒廊
瑞秋·亚当姆斯
到店日期  2019年4月1日
到店时间  晚间入住
离店日期  2019年4月2日
先生  先生
Sir‐‐ sir!
请从那里出来  这里属于私人财产
Please step away from there, that's private property.
是啊  哥们  那东西是隐私
Yeah, man, that stuff's confidential.
-不  你看  -我想是吧
- No‐‐ look. ‐ I think.
这个  看见了吗
This. You see?
这就是她的名字
That's her name right there.
这是她的名字  她入住了
That's her name, she's checked in.
她在哪  切斯特  你对她做了什么
Where is she, Chester, what'd you do with her?
出什么事了吗  拉瑞
Is something wrong, Larry?
-看见了吗  -放松一点
‐ Huh, you see? ‐ Just relax and just‐‐
等等  你为什么攥着拳头  拉瑞
wait, why you making a fist here, Larry?
老天  天哪
Oh! Oh, man! Ow, God!
你干了什么
What did you do?
我都没碰他
I didn't touch him!
先生  你还好吗
Sir, you all right?
我什么也没做
I didn't do anything!
-先生  你还好吗  -真没料到
- Sir, are you all right? ‐ I didn't see that coming.
先生  你还好吗  发生什么了
Sir, are you okay? What happened?
拉瑞  他打我
Larry. He hit me.
你不会真的打了他吧
Did you seriously just punch him?
-我妹妹在哪...  -别想了
‐ Where the fuck is‐‐ ‐ Not again.
先生  我得把你带回局里
Sir, I'm gonna have to take you in.
拉瑞
Larry?
瑞秋
Rachel?
拉瑞  怎么回...
Larry! What the‐‐
女士  请别动
Ma'am, stay there.
他要跟我一起回局里
He's coming with me.
警官  让他走吧
Officer, let him go.
这是我的错
It's my fault.
这个男人刚袭击了你
This man just assaulted you.
是我逼人太甚
Oh, I... I pushed him too far,
我整晚都在逗他
I've been winding him up all night.
老实说  我有点犯浑
Quite frankly, I've been a dick and
偷袭我的这拳算是便宜我了
I deserve a lot worse than getting sucker‐punched.
这么说你不打算起诉他
So you're not gonna press charges?
如果说这里有谁有罪  那也是我
If anyone's guilty of anything here, it's me,
搞了些没品位的恶作剧
of bad taste and shenanigans.
别想闹事  听到了吗
You gonna behave, son, hm?
听到了
Yes.
感谢上帝你没事
Thank God he's okay.
我不知道你俩是什么情况
Now, I don't know what's going on with you two,
但如果今晚我再回来
but if I got to come back here tonight,
我就把你俩都带走
I'm taking you both in.
-女士  -晚安
- Ma'am. ‐ Uh, goodnight.
他为难你了吗
Is he giving you a hard time?
是的  他一整晚都在耍我
Yeah, he's been playing these jokes on me all night.
拉瑞  太棒了  太棒了
Larry, that was great, that was great.
刚才那是什么情况
What the hell was that about, huh?
拉瑞非常担心你
Well, Larry was really worried about you,
然后他崩溃了给治安官打了电话
and then he freaked out and called the sheriff,
然后我使出了愚人节耍人招数
and then I pulled this great April Fools prank
并让警察走了
and got him to leave.
你叫治安官来抓他
You called the sheriff on him?
是的  我以为他对你做了什么
Yes, I thought that he did something to you.
什么叫做"对我做了什么"
What do you mean, did something to me?
-我就在这  好吗  -好吧
- I'm right here, okay? - Okay, well,
他知道你的名字  我不知道他
he knew your name, I didn't know that he‐‐
就是...
it's just...
瑞秋·亚当姆斯
到店日期  2019年4月1日
到店时间  晚间入住
离店日期  2019年4月2日
拉瑞  这是网上预定
Well, Larry, it's an online reservation.
我得写下名字才能订房间
You know, I had to put my name down to book the room.
它自己打印出来了
It prints out by itself.
我猜我该好好盯着  对吧
I guess I should do a better job of keeping an eye on that, huh?
好吧  放松
Humph. Hey, relax.
这是...
This is...
放松
Hey, relax.
看着我
Look at me.
-你怎么这么久才来  -天  发生了场大车祸
‐ What took you so long? ‐ Oh, God, there was a big accident,
我被堵在高速上于是我绕了一下
I got stuck on the freeway and I tried to do a detour.
迷路了  结果我想给你发信息
Got really lost, and then I tried to text you
但信息又发不出来
and it wouldn't send through.
我们忘掉这整件事吧  听到了吗
We're gonna forget this whole thing ever happened, you hear me?
你去好好睡一觉
And you're gonna get some sleep.
充充电  好好享受  房钱算我的
Recharge and enjoy the room on me,
尽管你偷袭给了我一拳
even though you sucker‐punched me.
我没有
I didn't.
你不需要和我握手
You don't have to shake my hand,
握手早就难表我们的情谊了  哥们
we're way beyond handshakes, buddy.
你也可以免费入住
And you could have a room for free too,
因为长得太美了
just for being so beautiful.
好吧  我不知道是怎么回事
Wow, okay, I don't really know what's happening,
但我喜欢
but I like it.
-我回房间了  -等等
‐ I'm gonna go to my room. - Uh, wait, um.
一开始见到你感觉很不爽
It was really upsetting meeting you at first,
但现在你看上去还不错
but you seem lovely now.
大家都这么说
A common refrain.
我怀疑这是不是他本人
I wonder if this is actually him.
不  这是性骚扰
No, it's sexual harassment is what it is.
"真好笑"
Ha ha.
我觉得不觉得这有趣
I just don't think that he's funny.
他也可以这么说你
Well, he could say the same thing about
叫警察来查他  你知道吗
you calling the cops on him, you know?
听着  我差不多算道过了歉
No, look, I mean, I kind of apologized.
好吧  也许他没有我想的那么坏
Okay, maybe he's not as bad as I thought.
这个婚礼让我心神不宁  知道吗
This wedding's really just messing with my head, you know?
我知道  来一口
I know. Here.
一切都会好的
It's gonna be all right, okay?
而且你应该把这个给辛迪
And you should give Cindy this.
-拿着  -我们应该请他去婚礼吗
- Take it. ‐ Should we invite him to the wedding?
三个火枪手
The Three Amigos?
走开
Go away!
"你好  辛迪
"Hey, Cindy.
这是我的巨根朋友切斯特
This is my giant cocked friend Chester.
你个操亲戚的婊子"
You cousin‐fucking bitch."
去吧  去开门
Go! Go get it!
是切斯特
It's Chester.
那开门吧
Well, open it.
-不  把灯关了  -他会看到了  老兄
‐ No, shut off the lights! ‐ He'll see, dude!
也许他能明白
Maybe he'll get the hint.
马上来
We're coming!
抱歉打扰  只是想来送几杯酒
Sorry for interrupting, just dropping off a couple drinks.
我猜今晚这些事后你们需要喝上一杯
Thought you might need them after the night you've had.
免费的
On the house.
晚安
Have a good night.
快说谢谢  他要走了
Say thank you, he's going.
等等  切斯特
Um, hey, hey, Chester?
谢了  哥们  这很贴心
Thanks, man, this is‐‐ it's really nice.
听着
And... listen,
再次抱歉  关于...
I'm sorry again about...
喊警察
Calling the cops?
打我脸
Punching me in the face?
别在意
Don't worry about it.
好吧
Okay. Uh...
不如我们和你一起喝一杯吧
Hey, why don't we join you for a drink?
不了  太晚了
Nah, it's late.
来吧  哥们  就一杯
Come on, dude, just one drink.
行吧  一杯
All right, one drink!
就一杯  两杯可不行
Just one, though, not two.
也许可以来九杯
Maybe nine.
我只是逗你玩呢
I'm just fucking with you.
我们可以来12杯  如果你愿意
We could have 12 if you want,
我都准备好了
I'm all set up.
好的
All right.
你想在那见吗
You want to meet there?
-所以你得留下它  -是的
- Aw, so you had to leave him. ‐ Yeah.
赫拉克勒斯只能和妈妈住在一起
Hercules had to stay with our mom.
那边不是很有禅意
It wasn't very zen out there.
我大概是西藏最没有禅意的人了
I was basically the least zen person in Tibet.
我从没冥想过
I've never been much for meditation.
我有过一个前女友想偷走我的心
I had an ex try to steal my mind once,
所以我只能偷走她的身体
so I had to steal her body.
这是个玩笑
It was a joke.
拜托  各位  放轻松点
Come on, guys, lighten up!
我上周还帮着她看狗来着
I just watched her dog last week.
她是个大婊子
She's a big bitch.
狗也很肥
Dog was fat, too.
你有正经的时候吗  还是...
So are you ever serious, or...
老天  医生来了
Oh boy, the doctor's in.
让我躺在沙发上
Let me just lay on the couch.
我要手淫两次然后明早打给你
I'll take two hand jobs and call you in the morning.
你这笑话讲得乱七八糟
The structure of that joke doesn't even make sense.
如果我是医生  应该是我给你开手淫的处方
Like, if I'm the doctor, I should be the one prescribing the hand jobs.
终于开窍了
Now we're getting somewhere.
这家伙怎么回事  小瑞
So what's this guy's deal, Rach?
他一直是这么一丝不苟吗
Has he always been, you know, uptight?
你应该见见他小时候的样子
Oh, you should have seen him when he was a kid.
他是最幽默最快乐的小孩了
He was the funniest, happiest little guy.
每分钟都在欢笑
Couldn't go two minutes without laughing.
大家都喜欢他
And everyone adored him.
后来怎么了
So what happened to him?
那个拉瑞还存在
Well, that Larry is still there,
只是现在只有我才能偶尔见见他
it's just that I'm the only one that gets to see it sometimes.
或也许他就是个混蛋
Or maybe he's just an asshole.
也许吧
Maybe.
他拿到啦
Whoa! He got it.
别秀了  你俩
Okay, you two.
我也希望自己能和谁这么亲密
I wish I had that kind of closeness with somebody.
你是什么来头  切斯特
So what is your story, Chester?
没什么来头
No story.
我就是个爱享受生活的家伙
I'm just a good‐time guy.
小酌几口  大笑几声
A few drinks, a few laughs.
鸡尾酒的制造者
I'm a maker of cocktails
玩笑的供应商
and a purveyor of jokes.
说实话  我一点也没受伤
To be honest, I'm not fucked up at all.
敬新朋友
To new friends.
*我们将携手共进*
*We'll be holding hands*
*直到世界末了*
*Until the end of time*
这次调得非常特殊
This is a very special batch.
不不不  我喝不了了
No, no, no, no, no, no, I can't do another one.
不不
No, no, no, no!
这次婚礼的真实故事是什么  老兄
So what's the real story with this wedding, man?
什么意思
Uh... like, how do you mean?
你看上去很沉重
You got a real heaviness about you.
整个人都紧张兮兮的
Your aura is all fumbled.
感觉你迫切地想释放些什么
Feel like you're dying to let something out.
跟我说实话
Level with me.
就是  就是这个姑娘
It's just... it's just this girl.
她叫什么名字
What's her name?
辛迪·休斯
Cindy Hughes.
她是唯一一个我想娶的姑娘
She's the only girl I ever wanted to marry.
但她甩了我
But she dumped me
在我想求婚的前一天
the day before I was gonna propose.
现在呢  她明天就要结婚了
And now, she's getting married tomorrow.
她要嫁给谁
Who's she marrying?
你不会相信的
You're never gonna believe this.
我的大哥
My first cousin.
我一直在想
You know, I keep wondering,
有什么比这更丢脸呢
like, what's more humiliating to
去参加婚礼  所有人都知道我们的关系
to go and know that everyone knows
不去参加
or to not go,
所有人又会在背后嘲笑我
knowing that everyone there is gonna be secretly laughing at me?
你需要做的  就是笑到最后
What you need to do is have the last laugh.
这场游戏要结束了  老兄
That's the end game, man.
失败者这样才能转败为胜
That's how the loser... wins.
你知道吗
You know,
其实我在思考做点什么
actually I was thinking about doing something.
在辛迪把我甩了之后
After Cindy dumped me,
我写了一封信来断绝我们的关系
I wrote the letter to end all letters.
我从没鼓起勇气把信交给她
Just never had the guts to give it to her,
但明天
but tomorrow,
明天我会给她的
tomorrow I will.
在她说出"我愿意"之前
Right before she says, "I do."
我能看看吗
Can I see it?
拜托  拉瑞  让我看看
Come on, Larry, let me see it.
我们好不容易有时间了  拉瑞
We're having a moment here, Larry.
来吧  拉瑞  让我看看
Come on, Larry, let me see it.
你不会再见到我了
You're never gonna see me again.
如果你抓住了正能量
I'll tell you if I think you...
我会告诉你的
captured the right energy.
我不会让别人看的
I've never let anyone read it.
连瑞秋都不行
Not even Rachel.
致辛迪  我不擅长言语
"Dear Cindy, words are really not my thing.
辛迪  我爱你  我从来没有那么爱过一个人
Cindy, I love you, I've never loved anyone..."
我爱你  小拉
Ah, I love you, Lar.
写的太棒了  老兄
That's fucking beautiful, man.
这会折磨死她的
It's gonna crucify her.
现在几点了
What time is it?
我不知道  很晚了
Uh, I don't know, it's late.
邦佐该睡觉了
Well, uh, bedtime for Bonzo.
我也要回去工作了
Yeah, I should probably be getting back to the desk.
天知道我错过了多少客户
Who knows how many customers I've missed.
好吧  晚安
All right, good night.
等一下
Oh, wait one sec.
我要给你照张相  你能过来吗
I need to get a picture of you, can you come here?
不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
我看起来像个矮松饼
I look like a scrub muffin.
别说了  你很好看
Shut up, you look amazing.
笑一笑  宝贝们
Smile, babies.
好的
Okay, all right.
晚安
Good night.
这张照片里的我很棒
That's a great picture of me.
但是...  就是...
But... just...
晚安  拉拉宝贝
Good night, Lar‐Bear.
我爱你  拉瑞
I love you, Larry.
接受好友申请
已成为朋友
什么鬼
What... the fuck?!
什么情况  不
What the hell, come on, no!
天啊
Jesus!
谁把你变成这样了
Who would do this to you?
-谁在...  -天啊
‐ Who is‐‐ oh, ah. ‐ Jesus.
-不  贝蒂  -这个人是谁
- Oh, no, Betty! ‐ Who is this guy?
-他只是个骑摩托车的  -贝蒂  不
- He's just this biker guy. ‐ Betty, no!
看起来切斯特这次太过了
It looks like Chester went too far this time.
是谁...  是谁干的
Who would‐‐ who would do this to you?
不  不  贝蒂
Not‐‐ not Betty!
你个该死的混蛋
You goddamn son of a bitch!
有问题吗  杰拉德
Is there a problem, Gerald?
我发誓
I swear to fucking Christ,
我一定要把这人的头拧下来
I'm gonna tear someone's fucking head off.
有人把你的坐骑"干了"啊
Oh, someone put a crotch on your crotch rocket.
是你干的吗
Did you do this?
你认为这很好笑吗
You think this is funny?
至少你不会和其他人的车搞混了
Oh, at least you won't mix it up with anyone else.
天啊
Jesus.
-不好笑  兄弟  -二位
- Not funny, man. - Guys.
-操你妈  -二位  二位  别打了
- Fuck you! - Guys, guys, stop it.
-是谁干的  -我们能聊聊吗
- Who would do this? ‐ Can we just talk about this?
你也想试试吗  小伙子
You want some of this, little man?
我要打死你  老兄
I'm gonna cut you up, man.
他在干什么
What's he doing?
切斯特
Chester.
我  只  是
I... was... just...
在逗  你  玩
fucking... with... you!
老天  老天
Oh man, oh man, oh man.
杰拉德  你还好吗
Gerald, are you okay?
杰拉德  有点过分了  兄弟
Gerald, things got carried away, man.
你还好吗  兄弟
Are you okay, man?
你还好吗
Are you okay?
You okay?
你还好吗  兄弟
You okay, man?
拜托  切斯特  拜托
Please, Chester, please.
你需要学会接受玩笑
You need to learn to take a joke.
切斯特
Chester.
你还好吗  杰拉德
You okay, Gerald?
你还好吗
Are you okay?
各位  我不觉得他还好
You guys, I don't think he's all right.
杰拉德  杰拉德
Gerald, Gerald!
发生了什么
What happened?
不
Ｏh, no.
该死  不
Oh, fuck, no.
他有把刀
He had a knife.
你看见了  对吧
You saw, right?
他要杀了我
He was gonna kill me.
杰拉德
Gerald!
他死了
He's dead.
我把他杀了
I killed him.
该死  我杀人了
Holy fuck, I fucking killed someone.
我们得报警
We have to call the police.
不
No.
不会出事的
Everything's gonna be all right.
不  会出事了
No, it won't.
我会处理好的
I'll take care of it.
你在...
What are you‐‐
你在干什么
what‐‐ what are you doing?
-别别别  -别  拜托
- No, no no no -- - No, please.
我来报警
I'll call.
一旦这个电话打通  我的生活会彻底改变
Once I make this phone call, it's gonna change my life.
拉瑞  我能求你帮我个忙吗
Larry, can I ask you to do something for me?
可以
O‐okay.
你能给我拿点伏特加吗
Will you go get me some vodka?
伏特加
Some vodka?
好的  好的
Okay, okay.
长途跋涉前的最后一杯酒
One last drink before the long walk.
好的  没问题
All right, okay.
喂  警察局吗
Hello, Sheriff's Department?
粉红汽车旅馆这里发生了一起惨案
There's been a tragedy at the Pink Motel.
我朋友死了
My friend is dead.
这是场意外
It was an accident.
办公室
天啊  我不敢相信现在发生的事情
Holy shit, I can't believe what the hell is happening right now.
我们得报警
We have to call the cops.
赶快
Now.
他说他已经报警了
He said that he was calling them already.
你觉得他真的报警了吗
You think he really made that call?
不知道  我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
把你手机给我
Give me your phone.
天啊  快点
God, come on.
-快打快打  -我在打
‐ Call, call, call, call, call. ‐ I am, I am.
911  你有什么紧急情况
9‐1‐1, what's your emergency?
你好
Hello, hi, uh, yeah,
我现在在粉红汽车旅馆酒廊
I'm calling from the Pink Motel and Lounge.
-我想上报...  -是的
‐ I wanted to report‐‐ - Um, yes,
治安官已经在路上了
the sheriff's already on his way.
你现在有危险吗
Are you currently in danger?
现在没有  但是
No, not this second, no, but, um, uh,
你能不能让他快一点
can you just make sure that he‐‐he's quick?
好的  我会告诉他的
Yes, I'll let him know.
好的  谢谢你
Okay, thank you.
我猜你是对的  他确实报警了
I guess you were right, he, uh, he made the call.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我在给他拿伏特加
I'm‐‐ I'm‐‐ I'm getting him that‐‐ that vodka.
什么
What?
我的天  我的天
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God!
看起来你们是约翰尼和雪莉
Looks like it's Johnny and Sherrie.
我知道你们现在可能在想
Now I know you're probably thinking
这对老夫妇惨死于
this elderly couple was horrendously murdered
他们自己经营的旅馆里
in the motel that they owned and operate.
你们猜对了  他们确实被杀了
And you're right, they were.
但不是被我杀的
But not by me.
原来约翰尼是世界级的变态
Turns out Johnny here was a world‐class pervert.
我喜欢看他们做爱
I like to watch 'em fuck.
他每个房间都装有隐藏摄像头
He had hidden cameras installed in every room.
傻缺们都不知道我在看着他们
Dumb fucks don't know I'm watching.
多年来他一直逍遥法外
And he was getting away with it for years
直到善良的老切斯特出现
until good old Chester came along
然后意识到丹麦有些地方烂透了
and realized that something was rotten in the state of Denmark.
我想明白了
I figured it out!
所以我和他当面谈了这件事
So I confronted him about it!
你是个坏人  约翰
You're a bad man, John!
我这么做的时候  雪莉感受到了背叛
And when I did, Sherrie felt the years of betrayal
这么多年她竟然不知道她的丈夫是个变态
of not knowing that her husband was a pervert
然后她拿出了一把刀
and she took out a knife.
我要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you!
然后她开始捅约翰尼
And she started stabbing Johnny.
我要先杀了你  婊子
Not if I kill you first, bitch!
然后他开始掐她脖子
And he started strangling her.
他们两个就在这里
And there they were, both of them,
交织在一起  拥抱着死去
intertwined in this... embrace of death.
互相杀了对方
Killing each other.
这是我这辈子见过的
It was the most honest expression of marriage
对婚姻最纯粹的表达
I've ever seen in my life.
但你们要相信我与这无关
But you gotta believe I didn't have anything to do with it.
你们相信我吗
Do you believe me?
我相信你  切斯特
Yeah, I believe you, Chester.
我倒杯酒给你
Let's get you that drink, huh?
我就知道我没喜欢错你
I knew there was a reason I liked this girl.
一人一杯
Shots all around.
你不会让我自己喝的
Well, you're not gonna make me drink this by myself.
我是对的
I was right.
杰拉德怎么说的来着
What was it that Gerald said?
别人给你倒的酒  你却不喝
It's rude to leave a drink that...
这很没有礼貌
someone poured for you.
对了  你还没告诉我你妹妹的名字
Oh, by the way, you never told me your sister's name.
我看了你脸书的主页
I looked on your Facebook page.
快跑
Run!
该死  我的钥匙在房间里
Fuck, my keys are in the room.
我的也在
Mine too.
我的房间  我的房间
My room, my room.
在这里
Over here.
我的天啊
Oh my God.
该死  钥匙在哪儿
Fuck, where the fuck are they?
我怎么会知道
How am I supposed to know?
-该死  -不
- Fuck. - No!
糟糕
Oh, shit.
我的天啊  我爹天
Oh my God, oh my God!
不不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
怎么了
What?
他还在那里
He's still there.
天啊
Oh, God.
我的天  我的天
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
天啊
Oh, God.
粉红汽车旅馆
我们得提醒治安官
We have to warn the sheriff.
算了吧  治安官讨厌我
Fuck that, that sheriff hates me.
治安官  你得帮帮我们
Sheriff, you have to help us!
别过来
Don't move.
什么  不
What? No.
不不不  我们之前跟您见过面  记得吗
No, no, no, it's just us from before, remember?
你们两个趴在地上  快点
The two of you on the ground now.
你没明白
You don't understand.
他已经疯了
He is crazy.
我给你们三秒钟
All right, you've got to the count of three.
一
One.
-二  -好吧
- Two. - Okay.
-三  -感谢你能过来  治安官
- Three. - Thank you for coming, Sheriff.
我的天  先生  你还好吗
My God, sir, are you all right?
发生了什么
What happened?
她用酒瓶子砸了我的脑袋
She hit me in the head with a bottle.
你用酒瓶子砸他脑袋了吗
Did you hit him in the head with a bottle?
是的
Yes.
但他杀了餐厅里的人
But... he killed those people in the diner,
而且他杀了人  尸体就在...
aAnd he killed a guy, the body's just...
该死
God damn it.
天啊
Oh, God.
我早就应该把你们关起来
I knew it was a bad idea not to take you in earlier.
脸朝下
Face down.
赶紧  趴在地上  快点
Right now, on the ground, now!
警官  不是我们干的
Officer, it wasn't us.
我要因为你帮助和教唆了一个白痴逮捕你
I'm taking you in for aiding and abetting an idiot.
站住  站住
Hey, hey, don't do it, don't do it, don't do it!
拉瑞
Larry!
别电了
Stop it, stop!
拜托停下来
Please stop!
你在笑什么
What are you laughing at?
我在逗你玩呢
I'm just fuckin' with you.
这是无价的
That was priceless.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
布这个局花了我很长时间
I mean, it took a lot of work to set this up.
我告诉过你他是个疯子
I told you, he's a psycho!
把嘴闭上
Hey, shut up.
你会有机会说话的  好吗
You're gonna get your chance, all right?
治安官  你还好吗
Sheriff, are you okay?
你还好吗  治安官
Are you okay, Sheriff?
你还好吗  你还好吗
Are you okay, are you okay?
你还好吗
Are you okay?
治安官  治安官  我来帮你
Sheriff, Sheriff, I'll help you.
你没事的  老兄
You're okay, man.
治安官  你还好吗
Sheriff, are you okay?
没事的
It's okay.
没事的  没事的
It's okay, it's okay.
没事的  会没事的
It's all right, it's gonna be okay.
会没事的  会没事的
It's gonna be okay, it's gonna be okay.
我从来没这么杀过人
Well, I never killed anyone like that before.
拉瑞  你得来看看
Larry, you gotta see this
起来  拉瑞
Get up, Larry.
你在干什么
What the fuck are you doing?
-我的错  -拉瑞  起来
- My bad. - Larry, Larry, get up!
-拉瑞  起来  -拉瑞  对不起
- Larry, get up. - Well, Larry, I'm sorry.
这个扳机松了  兄弟
This trigger's loose, man.
别再弄他了
Leave him alone!
停下来  停下来
Stop it, stop it!
不  你才应该停下来
No, you stop it!
别弄他了
Leave him alone.
拉瑞  我能帮你到车上去吗  老兄
Larry, can I help you to the car, man?
来  我给你开门
Here, I'll open the door for you.
拉瑞
Larry.
不  停下来
No! Stop!
该你了
Now you.
老天  拜托
Oh, God, please.
砰
Bang!
求你了
Please.
不
No.
那场手术很成功
The surgery was a success.
离我远一点
Get the fuck away from me!
滚开
Get away!
瑞秋  你要去哪儿
Rachel, where you going?
我只是想让你按时参加婚礼
I'm just trying to get you to the wedding on time.
你需要你的钥匙
You need your keys.
我只是想让你按时参加婚礼
I'm trying to get you to the wedding on time.
天啊
Oh, God.
拉瑞  你还好吗
Larry, are you okay?
天啊
Oh, God.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
启动发动机
-走走走  -我的天啊
- Go, go, go, go, go. - Oh, my God.
快走快走
Go, go, go, go, go.
走走走
你还好吗
Are you okay?
一路平安
Drive safe.
-操你妈  切斯特  -快走快走
- Fuck you, Chester! - Go, go, go, go, go, go.
我的天啊
Oh God.
他是个连环杀手
He's a fucking serial killer.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
这个声音是什么
What the fuck is that noise?
发生了什么
What's happening?
拜托
Come on!
Oh, come on!
什么情况
What the fuck.
天啊  天啊
Oh, God, oh, God.
快点  快点
Come on, come on.
不  快点
Oh, no, come on!
好吧
Okay, okay.
拉瑞  下来
Larry, get out.
快点  下来
Come on, come on.
-我扶着你  -我的老天
- I got you. - Oh my God.
我简直不敢相信居然奏效了
I can't believe it fucking worked.
快点  拉瑞
Come on, Larry.
起来  拉瑞  起来
Oh, get up, Larry, get up!
我现在斗志昂扬
I'm on fire.
天啊  拉瑞
Oh, God, Larry!
走
Go.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
二位  等等
Hey, guys, wait up!
走  快走
Go, go, go.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你在给他吸什么
What the fuck are you giving him?!
当然是笑气了
Laughing gas, of course.
不不不不  不要
No, no, no, no, no, don't, no, no, no!
不许动
Don't you fucking move!
不
No!
不不不
No! No, no.
一  二  三
One, two, three.
四
Four.
你这个
You fucking...
-五  -禽兽
- Five. - ...monster!
再加一个是六
One more is six.
放开我
Get off me!
*乖宝宝  不要哭闹了*
*Hush, little baby, don't say a word*
*切斯特会给你买荆棘鸟*
*Chester's gonna buy you a mockingbird*
你现在应该明白了  瑞秋
You should know by now, Rachel.
我只是在逗你玩
I was just fucking with you.
我死了吗
Am I dead?
朋友们  我们的特邀嘉宾醒了
My friends, our guest of honor is awake.
女士们先生们  拉瑞·亚当姆斯
Ladies and gentlemen, Larry Adams!
拉瑞  如果你滑下去
Larry, if you fall in,
可是会淹死的
you're gonna drown.
你现在手还动不了
You can't move your arms yet.
还不到时候
It's too soon.
放松  伙计
Just relax, my man.
我救不了你的
I won't be able to save you.
我不会游泳
I can't swim!
你是谁
Who are you?
我是法官
I am Judgment.
我是愤怒
I am Wrath.
你  拉瑞·亚当姆斯
And you, Larry Adams,
要被法官了
have been judgmented.
-根本没这种说法  -你怎么知道  拉瑞
- That's not a word. - How do you know, Larry?
你有同意替代词吗
Do you have a thesaurus on that raft?
我好难受
I don't feel well.
上帝啊  救救我
God help me.
上帝一直在救你  拉瑞
God is helping you, Larry.
他爱你
He loves you!
是他希望你变成这样的
This is the way He wants you to be.
欢迎来到我的夏威夷卢奥  拉瑞
Welcome to my Hawaiian luau, Larry.
你是我的特邀嘉宾
You are my guest of honor.
这是你的金花环
Here's your golden lei.
上帝啊
Oh, God.
听着  拉瑞
Listen, Larry.
我和你说实话
I'm not gonna lie to ya,
我让你服下了很多死藤水
I gave you a mega dose of ayahuasca...
还有些别的
and some other things.
你会感到很晕
You're gonna be feeling a little woozy.
你没事吧  伙计
You okay, man?
我是谁
Who am I?
我们今晚齐聚一堂就是为了弄清楚
That's why we're all gathered here tonight,
你到底是谁
to find out who you really are.
你不会有危险的  伙计
You're in a very safe space, man.
我是一名专业的萨满
I'm a trained shaman.
瑞秋在哪里
Where's Rachel?
瑞秋没事  伙计
Oh, Rachel's fine, man.
她只是在换泳衣
She's just changing into her bathing suit.
也许我们可以去看看她好了没
Perhaps we can go check on her.
让我们把仪式暂停一下
Let's put the ceremony on pause.
拉瑞宝贝
Listen, Lar-Bear,
我还需要你为我做一件事
there's one more thing I need for you to do.
对你的转化非常重要
It's very important for your transition.
好吧  什么事
Okay, what is it?
说实在的  你今晚算是
You kinda fucked things up for me tonight,
把我给毁了
if I'm being honest.
我本来计划了非常有意思的一晚
I had a fun evening planned,
然后你来了
and then you came along.
你简直就是稀有物种
You're the rarest of things.
什么意思
What do you mean?
你要明白
Understand this:
你是一个完全没有幽默感的人
You're a man completely devoid of a sense of humor.
你是一个暗藏毒刺的坏脾气鬼
You're a dour curmudgeon with a scorpion sting.
你就是愚人节的愚人
You're the April Fool.
没错
I am.
我知道
I know I am.
我希望你告诉我
I want you to tell me,
在你用毒品换来的新晋光环之下
in all your newfound, drug addled glory,
你到底是谁
who you really are.
告诉我拉瑞·亚当姆斯到底是谁
Tell me who Larry Adams is.
不是你用来遮掩的二重身份
Not the bullshit duality that you hide behind,
不是你呈现给世界的面具
not the mask you present to the world,
而是真正的你
but the real you.
真正的你
The real you.
好吧
Okay.
乖孩子
Good boy.
你想坐哪里
What do you think?
床上吗
On the bed?
我不知道
I don't know.
床上吧
Yeah, on the bed.
抱歉  我不是很会用摄像机
Sorry, I'm not much of a camera guy.
好吧
Okay.
好吧  我应该准备好了
Okay, I'm ready, I think.
那么  来说出真相吧
So, let the truth surge through you.
告诉我们俩  你到底是谁
Tell us both who you really... are.
开拍
And action.
我是一名键盘侠
I'm a troll.
我
I...
我就是一名键盘侠
Literally, I'm a troll.
外界看来
I mean, on the outside,
我光鲜亮丽  恭敬有礼
I'm I'm nice, I'm... meek,
平易近人
I'm affable,
但是内在
but on the inside,
我的内心充满污秽
my heart is full of bitterness.
我从来就没有融入过
I've never fit in.
我就像一直在玻璃墙的另一面
I'm on the other side of the glass,
觊觎着墙内的人们
always looking in.
太棒了  伙计
This is fantastic, man.
都发泄出来
Let it out.
继续
Continue.
我小时候
You know, when I was young,
我...我从来没办法自如地和其他孩子交流
I just...I never had the ability to talk to other kids.
我从来都不知道我该说什么
I never knew what to say.
我好像是囚禁在自己脑内的囚犯
It's like I'm a prisoner in my own head,
于是我非常憎恨他人
and it makes me hate people.
于是
So...
我创建了"编译缺陷"
I created ProgrammingFlaw.
编译缺陷
他能做到我永远做不到的事
He could do all the things that I never could.
吃全世界最小的鸡巴
我能得到自由
I could be free.
他按下按键就能摧毁别人
He can destroy people with a single push of a button.
听起来好像很厉害
Sounds like a hell of a guy!
没错
Oh, he is.
你的死亡高潮来得更快
他非常可怕
He's formidable.
埃博拉逼
他有我拥有不了的一切
He's everything that I'm not,
全世界只有他永远支持着我
and he's the only one who ever had my back,
除了瑞秋以外
Rachel aside.
谢天谢地  你还拥有她
Thank God you have her.
你会孤独死去
在我内心深处
Deep down in my soul,
我知道我是谁
I know who I am.
你是谁
So who are you?
我是编译缺陷
I'm ProgrammingFlaw.
卡
Scene.
来握个手  伙计
Lay it on me, man.
握手难表我们的情谊
We're beyond handshakes.
你完全接受了真正强大的自己
You fully embrace the real powerful you.
我为你自豪  缺陷
I'm proud of you, Flaw.
你成功了
You did it!
我现在能见瑞秋了吗
Hey, can I see Rachel now?
是这样的
Here's the deal.
所有动作
For every action,
都会有相同的作用力和反作用力
there's an equal and opposite reaction.
就是牛顿的第三定律
Newton's third law of motion.
瑞秋会称之为因果
Rachel would call it karma,
拉瑞会称之为报应
Larry would call it payback,
我称之为太他妈有趣了
I'll just call it fucking funny, man.
瑞秋  出来吧
Rachel, come on out!
她就在里面
She's just in there.
不不不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
不不不
No, no, no.
不
No!
不不不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不不不
No, no, no, no, no!
瑞秋
Rachel!
瑞秋  瑞秋  瑞秋
Rachel, Rachel, Rachel.
不
No!
你说她没事的
You said she was okay.
你明明保证过的
You promised me.
不然你没法完成转变  编缺陷
The transition wouldn't have worked otherwise, PFlaw.
不然你什么教训都得不到
You wouldn't have learned anything.
为什么
Why?
为什么不呢
Why not?
你知道比这更有趣的是什么吗
You want to know what's even funnier than this?
我刚刚把你那段可悲的独白
I just posted your pathetic confession
拉瑞·亚当姆斯
我是编译缺陷
以及那封撇脚的信发到婚礼论坛上了
and sappy letter to Cindy on the wedding forum.
亲爱的辛迪
我不擅长言语
辛迪  我爱你  我从来没有那么爱过一个人  我希望有朝一日  马克会像你摧毁我一样摧毁你  你会像我当初的每一天一样痛苦  直到你根本喘不上气
精选评论
Comment highlights:
"太可悲了  贱人
"Pathetic note, bitch.
她当然不会嫁给你了
Of course she'd never marry you.
滚吧  疯子
Get a life, freak.
你是不是有病"
What's wrong with you?"
"你真是太可悲了"
"You're just really pathetic."
这条不错
Oh, here's a good one.
就是"去死"
It just says, "Die."
这是辛迪本人的回复
And here's one from Cindy herself.
辛迪·休斯跟马克·亚当姆斯在一起
幸福  还有17个小时  #辛迪和马克的婚礼
准备好听了吗
Ready?
我是编译缺陷
"你是一个禽兽"  禽兽
"You are a monster..." ...A monster.
辛迪·休斯
你是一个禽兽  我从来就没喜欢过你  你真可悲
我从来没有喜欢过你  "你真可悲"
I never even liked you. "You're pathetic."
她真的很恨你  拉拉宝贝
She really hates you, Lar-Bear.
怎么了
What?
你知道吗
Do you know what?
我之前真是看错你了
I was wrong about you.
天啊  你这人真是太搞笑了
Oh my God, you are funny.
我...
I mean, I...
我...我知道了  我都知道了
I mean, I...I see it, man, I get it all now.
这一切真是太天才了
All of this was genius.
你简直就像是莫扎特  伙计
I mean, you're like Mozart, man.
你就像是喜剧界的莫扎特
You're like the Mozart of comedy.
我等你说这句话等了一晚上了
I've been waiting all night for you to say that.
你太逗了
You're hilarious.
你真是个搞笑的混蛋
I mean, you're a funny fucker.
这些人  杰拉德和治安官
I mean, those guys, Gerald and the Sheriff,
他们怎么回事
what is wrong with them?
他们现在也应该一起笑啊
They should've been laughing too, man.
那对死夫妻
Oh my God, that dead couple?
他们就是活该
I mean, they just flat-out deserved it.
等等  你现在正在拍吗
Oh, wait, are you filming this right now?
我们这些连环杀手就喜欢留纪念品
Oh, we serial killers like to keep souvenirs.
编缺陷  你真是为屠杀
PFlaw, you're a breath of fresh air
带来了清流
in a slaughterhouse.
但是所有的欢乐总有终点
But all good things must come to an end.
有最后的请求吗
Any last requests?
我不想死在这里
I don't want to die here.
我不想再活了
I mean, I don't want to live anymore.
但我不想死在这里
I don't want to die here.
我们去婚礼吧
Let's go to the wedding.
我们三个
All three of us.
有一座...有一座小山
I mean, there's...There's a hill
能俯瞰整个仪式
overlooking the festivities.
想象一下他们要是看到我们隆重登场
I mean, imagine the look on their dumbass faces
蠢脸上会有什么表情
when we rock up.
就我和瑞秋  两个死人
I mean, just me and Rachel, dead,
从山坡上滚向他们
just tumbling down a hill towards them.
马特·黑格曼
这该死的混蛋拉瑞·亚当姆斯竟敢毁了一切
那
Now that...
罗伯特·托马斯
拉瑞·亚当姆斯真的出现了  但他他妈的死了
凯莉·加西亚
天啊  这尸体是真的
那才叫搞笑呢
That would be fucking hilarious.
你在逗我玩吗
Are you just fucking with me?
你说呢
You tell me.
你要去哪里
Where you going?
我们开瑞秋的车
Let's take Rachel's car.
我来开
I'll drive.
-你想开车吗  -拜托  切斯特
- You want to drive? - Oh, come on, Chester.
瑞秋绝对不会让你开她的车
Rachel would never let you drive her car.
瑞秋  瑞秋
Rachel! Rachel!
你愿意让切斯特开你的车吗
Would you let Chester drive your car?
瑞秋说  "不可能"
Rachel says, "No fucking way."
拜托  切斯特
Come on, Chester.
你的气场好像有点凌乱
Your aura seems a little jumbled.
伙计  我只想说
Look, man, I just wanted to say,
谢谢你做的一切
thank you for everything.
钥匙
Keys.
出发
Let's roll.
我要干翻所有会动的玩意
I'll fuck anything that moves!
或者不会动的
Or doesn't move.
抱歉  瑞秋
Sorry, Rachel.
粉红汽车旅馆
瑞秋  你要上厕所吗
Rachel, do you have to pee?
切斯特  我能给你讲个笑话吗
Chester, can I tell you a joke?
当然了  伙计
Absolutely, man.
有两个笨蛋
So there's these two idiots,
开着车
and they're driving down the road.
然后呢
And?
他们的名字叫拉瑞和切斯特
Okay, and they're called Larry and Chester.
拉瑞的妹妹坐在车后
And Larry's sister is sittin' in the back,
一句话都不说
woop, not sayin' a word.
我已经开始喜欢了
I like it already.
瑞秋  安静听笑点  好吗
Rachel, be quiet for the punchline, okay?
然后拉瑞对切斯特说
And then Larry says to Chester,
"如果你现在可以成为世界上的任何东西
"If you could be anything in the world right now,
你会成为什么"
what would you be?"
然后  然后切斯特说
And...And Chester replies,
"我不知道  我要成为什么呢"
"Well, I don't know, what would I be?"
我不知道  要成为什么呢
I don't know, what would I be?
拉瑞说
"Well," Says Larry,
"你要成为瑞秋的狗"
"You'd be Rachel's dog."
瑞秋的狗
Rachel's dog?
没错
Yeah, that's right.
切斯特要成为瑞秋的狗  赫拉克勒斯
Chester would be Rachel's dog, Hercules.
然后切斯特说
Now Chester says,
我为什么要成为赫拉克勒斯
"Why would I be Hercules?"
Why would I be Hercules?
拉瑞说
"Well," Says Larry,
"瑞秋太爱赫拉克勒斯了
"Rachel just loved Hercules so much
所以她让它和她一起
that she had him ride up front with her
坐在前座"
in the passenger seat."
就是坐在你现在的这个位置
In fact, just right there in your seat right there.
你实在是太贴心了  瑞秋
Oh, you're so thoughtful, Rachel.
其实这样算是违法的
I mean, it wasn't exactly legal,
但是她就是太爱那只狗了
but she just loved that dog so much.
就像她爱我一样
Almost as much as she loved me.
她总是想要保护它的安全
She always wanted to keep him safe.
于是她改装了这辆车
So, she made an alteration to the car!
死路
笑点是什么  拉瑞
What's the punchline, Larry?
笑点是什么
What's the punchline?
切斯特
Oh, Chester.
笑点是  为了赫拉克勒斯
The punchline is that because of Hercules
瑞秋卸掉了这辆车一边的安全气囊
Rachel disabled the airbags on one side of the car,
就是切斯特那边的
Chester's side of the car.
现在我要开车撞向一堵墙
Now I'm gonna drive us into a fucking wall.
你不会的  拉瑞
You wouldn't, Larry.
你说得对
You're right.
拉瑞没有这胆子
Larry wouldn't have the balls.
但我是编译缺陷
But I'm ProgrammingFlaw.
敬美妙的笑声
To the beautiful sound of laughter.
加州警方通缉
拉瑞·亚当姆斯
32岁
男性
白人
涉嫌六起一级谋杀
加州警方通缉
拉瑞·亚当姆斯
32岁
男性
白人
初步验尸报告
瑞秋·亚当姆斯
谋杀
因注射漂白剂而死
被送到已死亡
粉红汽车旅馆杀手精神极度不稳定
44层下巴
最新新闻
粉红汽车旅馆惊悚监控录像泄漏
监控录像中为粉红汽车旅馆杀手拉瑞·亚当姆斯
他杀死自己的妹妹后  在地板上崩溃大哭  然后突然
该录像表明他当时的精神状态极度不稳定  包括现在也很有可能
警方称见到此人请不要接近他  马上报警
匿名回复  这段视频真恐怖  他还杀了那些人
杀死自己妹妹
不要接近
粉红汽车旅馆杀手屠杀后视频
拉瑞·亚当姆斯  杀死妹妹  连环杀手  小贱人
69%好评
粉红汽车旅馆屠杀
压抑恐怖
42.7关注者
瑞奇·霍普
那个键盘侠就该死  不能放过他
贾斯汀探姆5421
我知道他是杀人犯  但这也太搞笑了
搞笑
真是个可悲的家伙
卡里·卡萨西吗
恢复公开处刑吧
#混蛋该死#
#粉红汽车旅馆屠杀#
德里克·拉森
这个懦夫跟个小婊子似的跑了
编译缺陷3489
操你妈  下一个就是你
这些混蛋永远抓不住我
#吃爹大屌#
编译缺陷3489
给你讲个笑话
给你讲个笑话  我给你插我的屌
编译缺陷3489
等我用你男朋友的屌噎死你  再说说谁是小贱人
毛怪1126
等不及看这混蛋进监狱了
编译缺陷回复
等不及再监狱里干你这种人了
编译缺陷3489
编译缺陷干你的老婆女儿
你也可以看
一个
我只是逗你玩
I'm just fuking with you.
下
就
是
你